Guide to the Central Washington University Housing, Residence Hall Services, Kamola Hall Scrapbook 1965-1970
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Housing, Residence Hall Services, Kamola Hall Scrapbook
1965-1970
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG019-06-63
Central Washington University Housing
0.5 cubic feet 1 half sized document case and 1 note card box Photographs, newspaper clippings, and programs in good condition. Content removed from original acidic scrapbook mounts.
This collection contains the contents of a scrapbook created by female students of Kamola Hall, Central Washington University, 1965-1970.
Historical Note
Washington State Normal School, Central Washington University's predecessor, completed Kamola Hall in October of 1911. A dining room was added in 1915 and enlarged in 1919. The facility was originally used as a women’s dormitory. During the Second World War, Army Air Corps cadets used the dorms as barracks while training at the college and nearby airfield. During the 1990s, Kamola Hall served as a dorm for international students from Asia. The building was completely remodeled in 2002 and 2003 and is currently a co-ed dormitory for honor students.
Included in the Kamola Hall scrapbook are approximately 300 Polaroid photographs, both in black-and-white and color. Most of these photos date from 1965 to 1967. Along with original photographs, this collection includes preservation photocopies of original artwork which decorated the pages of the scrapbook, as well as newspaper clippings, flyers, programs and newsletters documenting events which took place on Central's campus and in Kamola Hall from 1965 to 1967.
The box list for this collection documents the contents of each scrapbook as it was found. Most of the photographs, etc., stayed secure to the mounts or picture corners of the book, but many were found loose. The processor numbered the photos on the page running from top to bottom and left to right. In some instances captions appeared without a corresponding photo--these captions are noted in the box list, as well as instances where a loose photo was positively matched to a caption. The box list also notes the original location of each item. Descriptions in quotes come directly from the scrapbook creator, while descriptions in brackets are those contributed by the processor for identification purposes. Three photos from the early 1990s were found loose at the front of the scrapbook. With the provenance to these photos unknown, the processor removed them for future placement within contemporary scrapbook / image collections.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Arranged by creator
Open to the public for educational research
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University Housing
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Universities and colleges--Washington (State); Dormitories
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
Photographic prints
College students
- Loose photos, 1 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 2 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 3 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 4 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 5 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 6 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 7 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 8 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 9 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 10 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 11 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 12 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 13 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 14 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 15 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 16 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 17 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 18 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 19 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 20 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 21 (Box-page 1)
- Loose photos, 22 (Box-page 1)
- Untitled, 25 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 26 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 27 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 28 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 29 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 30 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 31 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 32 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 33 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 34 (Box-page 1-1)
- Untitled, 35 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 36 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 37 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 38 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 39 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 40 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 41 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 42 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 43 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 44 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 45 (Box-page 1-2)
- Untitled, 46 (Box-page 1-2)
- Title for page: “Christmas 1965" by Joyce Barra, 47 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 48 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 49 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 50 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 51 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 52 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 53 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 54 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 55 (Box-page 1-3)
- Untitled, 56 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 57 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 58 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 59 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 60 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 61 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 62 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 63 (Box-page 1-4)
- Untitled, 64 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 65 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 66 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 67 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 68 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 69 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 70 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 71 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 72 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 73 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 74 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 75 (Box-page 1-5)
- Untitled, 76 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 77 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 78 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 79 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 80 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 81 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 82 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 83 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 84 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 85 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 86 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 87 (Box-page 1-6)
- Untitled, 88 (Box-page 1-7)
- Untitled, 89 (Box-page 1-7)
- Untitled, 90 (Box-page 1-7)
- Title page for section: “Let’s Take a Look at Spring Quarter," by Loretta Jensen. See artwork folder. (Box-page 1-8)
- Untitled (Box-page 1-9)
- “Lynn Hyatt, President", 91 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Vice President Susie Davis", 92 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Secretary Kathy Spencer", 93 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Carolyn Irby, Treasurer", 94 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Dorothy Byers and Bonnie Roberts Social Commissioners", 95 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Historian Loretta Jensen", 96 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Carlynn Kolbo, Courtesy Officer", 97 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Donna Jones, Song Leader", 98 (Box-page 1-10)
- MISSING: “Pep Chairman Margaret Mack", 99 (Box-page 1-10)
- “Susie Davis—Girl of the Month", 100 (Box-page 1-11)
- “New Wing Sponsors", 101 (Box-page 1-11)
- “Mrs. Ira Gray—Entertaining at One of the Dorm Meetings", 102 (Box-page 1-11)
- “Rosalie Millar, engaged", 103 (Box-page 1-11)
- Blank (Box-page 1-12)
- Blank (Box-page 1-13)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 104 (Box-page 1-14)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 105 (Box-page 1-14)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 106 (Box-page 1-14)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 107 (Box-page 1-14)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 108 (Box-page 1-14)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 109 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 110 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 111 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 112 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 113 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 114 (Box-page 1-15)
- Sweecy Day Events, 1966; 115 (Box-page 1-15)
- Coronation Ball—Miss Sweecy?, 1966; 116 (Box-page 1-16)
- Coronation Ball—Miss Sweecy?, 1966; 117 (Box-page 1-16)
- Title page for section: “Kamola Women in the New." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-17)
- “Queen Julie", 118 (Box-page 1-18)
- “Queen Julie", 119 (Box-page 1-18)
- Loose photo, 120 (Box-page 1-18)
- Title page for section: “Candy Dreams and Cupid Dust—Dorm Private Pajama Dance"--MISSING “The Squires", 121 (Box-page 1-19)
- “Cuddling", 122 (Box-page 1-19)
- MISSING “Dancing", 123 (Box-page 1-19)
- “Talking", 124 (Box-page 1-19)
- “Eating", 125 (Box-page 1-19)
- “Recuperating", 126 (Box-page 1-19)
- Title page for section: “Winter Quarter, 1967" by Loretta Jensen. See artwork folder (Box-page 1-20)
- “Becky Young, New [Dorm] Librarian", 127 (Box-page 1-21)
- MISSING “Loretta Telling AWS News", 128 (Box-page 1-21)
- MISSING “Mr. Hill: Kamola’s Future Plans", 129 (Box-page 1-21)
- MISSING “Patty Burkhart, Shelly Schrock: Beauties Preparing for a Night Out", 130 (Box-page 1-21)
- “Dorothy Nelson, Frosh Representative", 131 (Box-page 1-21)
- MISSING “We don’t mind y__ cutting hair girl ___ but what’s that under the chair? Barber: Dotty / Victim: Dorothy W?", 132 (Box-page 1-21)
- Blank (Box-page 1-22)
- Title for page: “Christmas"--MISSING “Judy Sn__der, Dawn Beck, Marcia Ferris “Kamola’s Woodcutters", circa 1967; 133 (Box-page 1-23)
- Three stockings over the mantle, 134 (Box-page 1-23)
- MISSING “We don’t want just any ornament!", 135 (Box-page 1-23)
- “Mrs. Santa (Jay Graham), Santa (Wanda Rabb), Pixie (Connie Escalvon), 136 (Box-page 1-23)
- MISSING “Hey, Nancy! Don’t just sit there. Give us a hand!", 137 (Box-page 1-23)
- “Mrs. Santa tells ‘The Night Before Christmas’ as reindeers (Rue=Sue Boyd and Dolf=Jo Boyd) watch on.", 138 (Box-page 1-23)
- “Terry Blair: It’s a lot of work, but…", 139 (Box-page 1-23)
- “Mom (Jan Deglow) in her nightgown and Pop (Dawn Beck) in his night cap.", 140 (Box-page 1-23)
- “It’s worth it in the end" FOUND: [see number #19], 141 (Box-page 1-23)
- “Guests watching Choral Competition singers", 142 (Box-page 1-23)
- Miss Sweecy Pageant. Row of contestants, 1966; 143 (Box-page 1-24)
- “Lorri Moisio", 144 (Box-page 1-24)
- “Mary Ellen Bugni", 145 (Box-page 1-24)
- “Susie Davis", 146 (Box-page 1-24)
- Title for page: “Happy Birthday, Mom Stroup!" (Box-page 1-25)
- Parent’s Weekend--found loose on page. See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-25)
- Program for musical "Wonderful Town." See folder. (Box-page 1-25)
- “J.P.: Winner of the Dorm Scholarship", 147 (Box-page 1-25)
- “Mrs. Ira Gray and Donna Jones singing for Parent’s Weekend. Bootie Bailey as accompanist", 148 (Box-page 1-25)
- MISSING, 149 (Box-page 1-25)
- “Mom Stroup", 150 (Box-page 1-25)
- “Mom Stroup", 151 (Box-page 1-25)
- “Mom Stroup", 152 (Box-page 1-25)
- Program for Parent’s Weekend--found loose on page. See folder., 1966 (Box-page 1-26)
- Play Set for Closing Night. See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-26)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 153 (Box-page 1-27)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 154 (Box-page 1-27)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 155 (Box-page 1-27)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 156 (Box-page 1-27)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 157 (Box-page 1-27)
- Candid shots of dorm life, 158 (Box-page 1-27)
- MISSING “Part Time Again", 159 (Box-page 1-27)
- Blank (Box-page 1-28)
- "Gals Compete" and "Spurs Induct 35 CWS Coeds." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 160 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 161 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 162 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 163 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 164 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 165 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 166 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 167 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 168 (Box-page 1-29)
- Loose photos, 169 (Box-page 1-29)
- End of school year, 170 (Box-page 1-30)
- End of school year, 171 (Box-page 1-30)
- End of school year, 172 (Box-page 1-30)
- Title page for section: “Fall Quarter, 1966," by Loretta Jensen. See artwork folder. (Box-page 1-31)
- Moving back into the dorm, 173 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 174 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 175 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 176 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 177 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 178 (Box-page 1-32)
- MISSING: “Demandatory = Beanies. (Remember, Frosh?) Optional? Sweatshirts.", 179 (Box-page 1-32)
- Moving back into the dorm, 180 (Box-page 1-32)
- Untitled, 181 (Box-page 1-33)
- Untitled, 182 (Box-page 1-33)
- Untitled, 183 (Box-page 1-33)
- Untitled, 184 (Box-page 1-33)
- MISSING, 185 (Box-page 1-33)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 186 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 187 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 188 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 189 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 190 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 191 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 192 (Box-page 1-34)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 193 (Box-page 1-35)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 194 (Box-page 1-35)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 195 (Box-page 1-35)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 196 (Box-page 1-35)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 197 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 198 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 199 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 200 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 201 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 202 (Box-page 1-36)
- Frosh Orientation Events, 203 (Box-page 1-36)
- “Connie Slater, Barb Turosik and engaged", 1967; 204 (Box-page 1-37)
- Freshman Orientation, 1967; 205 (Box-page 1-37)
- Freshman Orientation, 1967; 206 (Box-page 1-37)
- Freshman Orientation, 1967; 207 (Box-page 1-37)
- Title for page: “1967 Inititation Banquet, Mrs. Hebeler came as guest." See #211, 213 and 213a. (Box-page 1-38)
- Title on page: "Homecoming", 215 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 216 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 217 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 218 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 219 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 220 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 221 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 222 (Box-page 1-39)
- Untitled, 223 (Box-page 1-39)
- Christmas folder, found loose, 224 (Box-page 1-40)
- Christmas folder, found loose, 225 (Box-page 1-40)
- “J.P. and Mike—Kamola’s Sweethearts", 226 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Conference?", 227 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Engagement—Carolynn Irby, Pam Foster, and Virginia Beebe’, 228 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Mr. and Mrs. Santa Claus and Little Self Helper", 229 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Choral competition girls perform for the Kamola Christmas Party", 230 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Christmas, 1967", 231 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Assistant Housemothers: Marianne, Sharon, Lurene and Joyce receive their Christmas gifts", 232 (Box-page 1-40)
- Gift giving, including one to Mrs. Woodowitz, 233 (Box-page 1-40)
- Gift giving, including one to Mrs. Woodowitz, 234 (Box-page 1-40)
- Gift giving, including one to Mrs. Woodowitz, 235 (Box-page 1-40)
- Gift giving, including one to Mrs. Woodowitz, 236 (Box-page 1-40)
- Gift giving, including one to Mrs. Woodowitz, 237 (Box-page 1-40)
- “Jan Deglow and Margi Sakai {Sakaii?}—Girls of the Month", 238 (Box-page 1-41)
- “Cindy Havigg sings for us", 239 (Box-page 1-41)
- “No Necking?", 240 (Box-page 1-41)
- “No Drinking?", 241 (Box-page 1-41)
- “No Checking Out?", 242 (Box-page 1-41)
- “No Loud Noise? Oh no—no fun!", 243 (Box-page 1-41)
- “Carolynn Irby plays the tambourine", 244 (Box-page 1-41)
- Title for page: “Christmas, 1966", 245 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 246 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 247 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 248 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 249 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 250 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 251 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 252 (Box-page 1-42)
- "Who’s Who Honors Elite CWS Students" and "Central ROTC Unit Presents Military Ball", 253 (Box-page 1-42)
- Title for page: “Lovely Ladies of Kamola", 254 (Box-page 1-43)
- Kamola Hall Newsletter. See newsletter folder., 1966; 255 (Box-page 1-43)
- Kamola Hall Newsletter. See newsletter folder., 1966; 256 (Box-page 1-43)
- Kamola Hall Newsletter. See newsletter folder., 1966; 257 (Box-page 1-43)
- Homecoming, 1966; 261 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 262 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 263 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 264 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 265 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 266 (Box-page 1-44)
- Homecoming, 1966; 267 (Box-page 1-44)
- Kamola Hall Newsletter, pg. 2-4 of ?, 1966 (Box-page 1-45)
- Homecoming Queen competition, 268 (Box-page 1-46)
- Homecoming Queen competition, 269 (Box-page 1-46)
- Homecoming Queen competition, 270 (Box-page 1-46)
- Homecoming Queen competition, 271 (Box-page 1-46)
- Homecoming Queen competition, 272 (Box-page 1-46)
- "Homecoming Entertainment Flyer." Homecoming news clippings. See news clippings folder., 1966 (Box-page 1-47)
- Title for page: “New Student Week", 273 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 274 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 275 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 276 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 277 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 278 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 279 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 280 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 281 (Box-page 1-48)
- New Student Week, 282 (Box-page 1-48)
- Title for page: “Upper Classmen Arrive Early for Preparation", 283 (Box-page 1-49)
- Upper classmen, 284 (Box-page 1-49)
- Upper classmen, 285 (Box-page 1-49)
- Upper classmen, 286 (Box-page 1-49)
- Upper classmen, 287 (Box-page 1-49)
- Upper classmen, 288 (Box-page 1-49)
- "Military Ball Deemed Best By Everyone." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-50)
- 75th Anniversary Celebration Program for “Susannah: An American Opera by Carlisle Floyd." See folder. "Drama Club Produces Children’s Moon Tale." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-51)
- “Linda Harris as Goldsmith’s Daughter", 289 (Box-page 1-51)
- Untitled, 290 (Box-page 1-52)
- Untitled, 291 (Box-page 1-52)
- Title to page. “Mom Stroup." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-53)
- “New Girls, Fireside", 292 (Box-page 1-54)
- MISSING, 293 (Box-page 1-54)
- Girls with sheet cake, 294 (Box-page 1-54)
- “Sandy Withrow—Girl of the Month. Girls of the Month previously: Dorothy Beyers and Bonnie Roberts", 295 (Box-page 1-54)
- “Susie gets her candle", 296 (Box-page 1-54)
- “Engaged Laura Parker, Susie Davis, Jayna Zgone, Kay Gray", 297 (Box-page 1-54)
- “Donna Jones—Girl of the Month", 298 (Box-page 1-54)
- “Engaged—Judy Behrens", 299 (Box-page 1-54)
- "Engaged—Jan Leggett and Margi Byars", 300 (Box-page 1-54)
- George Lincoln Rockwell Amuses, Provokes, Angers. See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-55)
- Title for page: “Campaigns", 301 (Box-page 1-56)
- Campaigns, 302 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Karen Kirsch and Kathy Bramer’s skit", 303 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Wanda Rabb’s skit", 304 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Loretta Jensen’s skit", 305 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Margi Sakaii’s skit", 306 (Box-page 1-56)
- Campaigns, 307 (Box-page 1-56)
- Campaigns, 308 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Judy Snyder’s skit", 309 (Box-page 1-56)
- “Jan Deglow’s skit", 310 (Box-page 1-56)
- Campaigns, 311 (Box-page 1-57)
- “Connie and Jay", 312 (Box-page 1-57)
- “Wanda Rabb", 313 (Box-page 1-57)
- “Julie Pomeroy", 314 (Box-page 1-57)
- “July Snyder", 315 (Box-page 1-57)
- Campaigns, 316 (Box-page 1-57)
- MISSING: “Time for Shower!", 317 (Box-page 1-57)
- “Installation Banquet" for elected and appointed officers, 318 (Box-page 1-58)
- “Installation Banquet" for elected and appointed officers, 319 (Box-page 1-58)
- “Installation Banquet" for elected and appointed officers, 320 (Box-page 1-58)
- MISSING “New Appointed Officers", 321 (Box-page 1-58)
- “Installation Banquet" for elected and appointed officers, 322 (Box-page 1-58)
- “Installation Banquet" for elected and appointed officers, 323 (Box-page 1-58)
- Dorm Officers, 324 (Box-page 1-59)
- “Maralee Sifferman, Pep Chairman", 325 (Box-page 1-59)
- “Val Hinthorne, Song Leader", 326 (Box-page 1-59)
- “Bridget Foley, Courtesy Chairman", 327 (Box-page 1-59)
- “Barb Turosik, Library Board", 328 (Box-page 1-59)
- “Penny Thompson, Editor", 329 (Box-page 1-59)
- Officers and award winners, 330 (Box-page 1-60)
- “Penny Hoag—Girl of the Month", 331 (Box-page 1-60)
- Officers and award winners, 332 (Box-page 1-60)
- Officers and award winners, 333 (Box-page 1-60)
- “Graduating Seniors—LeAnn Pauley, Lynn Novetney, and Ronnie Fernandsee", 334 (Box-page 1-60)
- “Linda Huntington and Charlene", 335 (Box-page 1-60)
- Officers and award winners, 336 (Box-page 1-61)
- Officers and award winners, 337 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Singing—Jay Graham, Mary Fast, and Connie Esclavon", 338 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Cindy Haavig sings for us", 339 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Mrs. Stroup gives Judy—the New Pres.—a gift.", 340 (Box-page 1-61)
- Officers and award winners, 341 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Outgoing Pres. Lynn Hyatt and newly elected President Judy Snyder", 342 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Outgoing Historian Loretta Jensen and newly appointed Cindy Harrison", 343 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Outgoing Social Commissioners: Dorothy Byers and Bonnie Roberts", 344 (Box-page 1-61)
- “Joyce Barra and Sharon Greaby. Assistant Housemothers that are leaving.", 345 (Box-page 1-61)
- Kamola Girls Newsletter. One page. See newsletter folder., 1966 (Box-page 1-62)
- “Sharon Greaby—engaged", 346 (Box-page 1-62)
- "Foreign Students View Cultural Differences" and "Ferrante and Teicher Perform at CWU." See news clippings folder. (Box-page 1-62)
- Blank (Box-page 1-63)
- Title page for section: “Fall Quarter, 1967" by Dawn Beck (Box-page 1-64)
- "Miss Raaum Reigns in Ellensburg." Miss Ellensburg Pageant. See news clippings folder., 1967 (Box-page 1-65)
- “Jan Deglow getting straightened up", 347 (Box-page 1-65)
- Girl at bathroom mirror; found loose on page, 348 (Box-page 1-65)
- Man in front of film screen. See #129., 349 (Box-page 1-65)
- “Jan Deglow accepts 1st prize for floor decorations on 2nd-long for Homecoming", 350 (Box-page 1-65)
- “Linda Blair", 351 (Box-page 1-65)
- Title for page: “Up, Up and Away…" Three news clippings about Homecoming Queen from Kamola, Jeannette Graham (Box-page 1-66)
- Girl in beanie and girl in suit doing a skit; page remnant, with only this one photo on it, 352 (Box-page 1-67)
- Blank (Box-page 1-68)
- Title page for section or perhaps for entire book: “Moments to Remember." See artwork folder. (Box-page 1-69)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 353 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 354 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 355 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 356 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 357 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 358 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 359 (Box-page 1-70)
- Dorm life, 1967-1970; 360 (Box-page 1-70)
- Blank (Box-page 1-71)